You can pre-order certain Xbox One games through the Xbox Store
and install the digital version before the release date.
Browse or search the Xbox Store to find the game you want.
On the game’s details page, select Pre-order if it's available.
After you buy the game, it's installed if the game is ready,
or else it’s added to your download queue until closer to the release day.
You’re charged at the time of pre-order.
If you want to cancel before the release date, contact Xbox Support.
Go to support.xbox.com/contact-us for information.
You’ll be able to start playing the game as soon as it’s released in your region,
usually at 12:00 A.M. local time on the release date.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.